http://www.centronic.co.uk/privacy

History
Founded in 1945 by Gilbert Tomes and Alec Tidmarsh, Centronic, or Centurion Tubes as it was then known, started life in the back bedroom of Gilbert Tomes' house in Kent, England.
Read more...
Capabilities & Facilities
Capabilities & Facilities
Centronic’s expertise covers all aspects of production, complete in-house design & manufacturing, machining and environmental testing to final test/inspection, thereby maintaining complete control of all operation sequences.
Read more...
Our Customers
Our Customers
Centronic has decades of experience of supplying the biggest names in our chosen industries.
Read more...
Need to speak to someone?
Contact Name
Centronic Limited
Contact Tel. 0044 1689 808000
Email them here
PRODUCTS
Silicon Photodiodes
General purpose
Infra-red
Motor Assembly
Need to speak to someone?
Contact Name
Centronic Limited
Contact Tel. 0044 1689 808000
Email them here
MARKETS
Nuclear
Nuclear
Centronic Limited has been supplying to the Nuclear Industry since the 1950s. As the first company worldwide to supply radiation detectors to nuclear reactors for commercial electricity generation, Centronic is still a trusted supplier to some of the...
Read more...
Aerospace
Aerospace
As a provider of Silicon photodiodes for cockpit display lighting control and communication systems, Centronic has significant experience of supplying the Aerospace industry, and meeting its exacting quality requirements. We also supply electromagnet...
Read more...
Defence
Defence
Centronic Limited has supplied silicon photodiode products to some of the biggest defence companies in the world. Our products have been used in Laser Ranger and Marked Target Seeker projects, weapon simulator systems, and cockpit and display lightin...
Read more...
Research
Research
Centronic has close relationships with many research facilities worldwide, and provides detectors for measurement and environmental control for research establishments studying materials utilising particle physics, synchrotron, fusion and fission tec...
Read more...
Industrial
Industrial
Centronic supplies detectors worldwide for Instrumentation covering diverse applications including spectrometry, non-destructive testing, particle analysis and characterisation, metrology, high temperature measurements, colour and pattern recognition...
Read more...
Space
Space
Centronic has worked on projects for many key customers in the space industry, providing silicon photodiodes for sun acquisition sensors for launch vehicles for various space exploration projects. We have also supplied detectors for imaging systems f...
Read more...
Oil and Gas
Oil and Gas
Centronic is a key supplier of Geiger Muller tubes for intrinsically safe personnel and area dosimeters, nuclear density gauges for oil separation, well logging and fluid level measurement instrumentation.
Read more...
Medical
Medical
Centronic detectors are used widely in medical applications, for applications such as x-ray monitoring (CT systems), blood glucose and haemoglobin monitoring, radiological imaging, H&S and environmental and waste management.
Read more...
Need to speak to someone?
Contact Name
Centronic Limited
Contact Tel. 0044 1689 808000
Email them here
NEWS & EVENTS
News
Congratulations to our Apprentices, Jeryll and Taylor!
Well done to Jeryll (Precision Assembly Technician) and Taylor (CNC Machinist) for completing year 1 of their apprenticeships, gaining an NVQ Level 2 qualification in Performing Manufacturing Operations. It's a fantastic achievement.
Read more...
Events
Need to speak to someone?
Contact Name
Centronic Limited
Contact Tel. 0044 1689 808000
Email them here
CAREERS
Employment opportunities
CNC Turner Programmers/Setters/Operators
The purpose of the role is to programme, set and operate lathes. The ideal candidate will have experience of using Siemens and XYZ Pro-Track control, but experience in other controls will be considered and training will be provided.
Read more...
Why Join Us
Why Join Us
Based in Croydon, London UK, Centronic is a well-established engineering and manufacturing business. Serving a range of exciting and demanding industries, and working closely with some of the largest companies in the world, we are always keen to hear...
Read more...
Need to speak to someone?
Contact Name
Centronic Limited
Contact Tel. 0044 1689 808000
Email them here
CONTACT US
How to find us
How to find us
Centronic Limited – Head Office,Centronic House,King Henry's Drive,Croydon,Surrey CR9 0BG
Read more...
Agents & Distributors
Agents and Distributors
No matter where ever you are located in the world Centronic Ltd are always happy to help, however If you prefer to contact someone closer to home, we have many distributors throughout the world.
Read more...
Enquiries
Centronic
Centronic House
King Henry's Drive
Croydon
CR9 0BG
info@centronic.co.uk
0044 1689 808000
Need to speak to someone?
Contact Name
Centronic Limited
Contact Tel. 0044 1689 808000
Email them here
Home
Privacy
Privacy
Please read our terms and conditions carefully before using our website.
Proceeding to use the website will indicate your acceptance of the following terms and conditions. If you wish to use any services produced online now or in the future, you are also subject to the applicable terms. We reserve the right to change the website and these terms and conditions from time to time without notice to you, and your continued use of the website indicates your continued acceptance of the terms and conditions as modified.
Communications with Website Users
Cookies
Your Web browser may allow you to be notified when you are receiving a cookie, giving you the choice to accept it or not. By not accepting cookies, some pages may not fully function and you may not be able to access certain information on this site.
Copyright Notice
This website and the information contained within it is protected by copyright. Reproduction of part or all of the website contents in any form is prohibited unless for personal use. Content of this website may not be copied to any other publication (including electronic, hard copy or others). Interior deep linking or framing of this website is prohibited without permission of Centronic.
Data Protection Notice
Centronic is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 and complies with the Act in all our dealings with your personal data.
Disclaimers
The information contained in this website contains opinions and indicators only which are not intended to be relied upon to make business decisions. Centronic makes no warranties, representations or undertakings about (1) the content of this website or (2) the content of any other website referred to or accessed by hyperlink. Whilst we will endeavour to maintain our online services, we cannot guarantee that this website will always be accessible to you nor can we guarantee that services provided by this website will not be interrupted. Furthermore, whilst we operate strict internal procedures regarding the integrity of the website, we cannot promise that any information that you may download or copy will be error or virus free. For the avoidance of doubt, we disclaim responsibility for any damages that may be caused to you as a result of using this website as well as any damages third parties may cause to you by your use of this website resulting from a breach of website security.
Privacy Policy
The legal details that the Centronic web site adheres to are outlined below. Please read them before using the web site.
Data Protection
1. Centronic will process your personal data in accordance with data protection legislation.
2. You hereby agree that any information sent to Centronic by you or otherwise obtained by Centronic about you ("Personal Data") may be processed by Centronic for the purposes of:
(a) answering your requests and sending you information by email or post;
(c) providing you with information about products and services from Centronic;
(d) providing a personalised service;
(e) maintaining and administering client accounts and records;
(g) statistical analysis and conducting market research surveys;
(h) assessing and evaluating the use that is being made of the Centronic;
3. THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA MAY INVOLVE Centronic DISCLOSING YOUR DETAILS TO REGULATORY BODIES AND/OR OTHER THIRD PARTIES. If you do not wish your Personal Data to be disclosed in this manner, please send a clear email to Centronic (info@centronic.co.uk).
4. You also consent to the transfer, storage and processing of the Personal Data to/in countries outside the European Economic Area in connection with the processing mentioned above. Your Personal Data may therefore be processed in countries where the rights and benefits conferred on data subjects may not be as favourable as in the UK and the European Union. If you would prefer not to have your Personal Data transferred in this way, please send an email to Centronic (info@centronic.co.uk).
5. The Centronic site may use cookies for collecting user information and the data collected in this way may be processed in the same way as other data submitted to Centronic (and outlined above) and for the same purposes.
6. From time to time we may also notify you of other goods and/or services offered by Centronic or other branches of Centronic. If you prefer not to receive such offers or details, or if you do not wish your Personal Data to be processed in the manner outlined above, please make this clear by emailing Centronic (info@centronic.co.uk).
Privacy
Home
About Us
Contact
Why Join Us
Markets
Privacy
Product Groups
Need to speak to someone?
